Roie Shlosberg

21/01/1991 10 Aharon Yariv st, Holon +972-50-3210191 rshlosberg@gmail.com

Profile:

Java software developer with 2 years of experience with emphasis in object-oriented analysis, design and programming of client applications with java and also more than nine months' experience of development a native Android mobile application.

Looking for a challenging role in the fields of Java, Android mobile development and/or Big Data.

Experience:

2016-2017: Freelance Android Developer

- Development of an Android mobile application, called "Almost Shabbat" ("אוטוטו שבת" in Hebrew), for notify users about shabbat and holidays candle lighting times.
- Link: https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.candle_lighting
- This app has been published on the Play store of Google and has, as of this writing, hundreds
 of users in more than 100 different communities in Israel, and couple of users abroad
 (mainly in the United States, Europe and South America).
- Query a dedicated web service, which supply a JSON file that holds all required jewish calendar information, and parse this JSON file.
- Division the different tasks into separate services, handler threads and broadcast receivers.
- The app is available in Hebrew, English, French, Russian and Spanish.
- Development through using of relevant design patterns.
- Worked independently.

2013-2016: BI Developer, Ofek Unit IAF

- Development and maintenance of an operational system for maintenance data analysis.
- Implementing interface of bringing data from a source system db to our system db.
- Maintaining enterprise-wide data warehouse.
- Development of OBIEE dashboards, based on a characterization.
- Played a major role in a large scale project of building a new information system from the ground up in order to replace a 40 years old legacy system.
- Played a responsibility of the team's operational systems role, including managing the current response to fix urgent problems.

2011-2013: Java Software Developer, Ofek Unit IAF

- Development of a desktop pre-production application for analyzing large amount of data.
- Integrating Matlab scripts with dedicates interpreter.
- Hands-on development of a Swing GUI infrastructure and JDBC manipulations.
- Agile development with Scrum elements.

Profession knowledge:

Programming Language: Java, PL/SQL

Java: OOP, J2EE (JDBC), SWING, Java 8th Edition

DB: PL/SQL, Oracle ETL Tools: Informatica

BI Tools: OBIEE 11g, Oracle BI Administration Tool (RPD)

Other Tools: Android SDK, Android Studio, GIT, NetBeans IDE, Clear Case, JIRA, MATLAB

Platforms: Windows

Education:

2013 – 2017: Diploma in computer science (In progress) – Open University

2007 – 2010: BSc in Industrial Applied Mathematics - HIT (Holon Institute of Technology)

Expertise: signal and image processing

• Dean's Honor - on the year 2010

Courses and Trainings:

JOHN BRYCE - Advanced Oracle, User Experience Design BASMAH, IDF - Design Patterns, Basic Oracle, DB Design Ness College - CTM-Ed (Certification Technology Management)

Languages:

Hebrew – Mother tongue level English – Good level